const ques=[
    {
        question:"Which famous character is also a Nuclear physicist?",
        options:["Bruce Banner","Natasha Romanoff","Tony Stark","Peter Parker"],
        ans:"Bruce Banner"
    },
    {
        question:"What is Thor's hammer called?",
        options:["Titan","Mjolnir","Stormbreaker","Arc Reactor"],
        ans:"Mjolnir"
    },
    {
        question:"For how many years was Steve Rogers frozen?",
        options:[43,100,70,66],
        ans:66
    },
    {
        question:"Where did Gamora die?",
        options:["Asgard","Xandar","Earth","Vormir"],
        ans:"Vormir"
    },
    {
        question:"What is Captain America's shield made up of?",
        options:["Mysterium","Neutonium","Vibranium","Cavorite"],
        ans:"Vibranium"
    },
    {
        question:"What is Black Panther's real name?",
        options:["Clint Barton","Howard Stark","T'Challa","Peter Quill"],
        ans:"T'Challa"
    },
    {
        question:"What does Tony Stark call his AI assistant?",
        options:["JARVIS","Aunt May","SHIELD","HulkBuster"],
        ans:"JARVIS"
    },
    {
        question:"What is the name of Thor's home planet?",
        options:["Vormir","Ego","Knowhere","Asgard"],
        ans:"Asgard"
    },
    {
        question:"Whos is Loki's adoptive father?",
        options:["Korg","Bruce Banner","Odin","Thor"],
        ans:"Odin"
    },
    {
        question:"What country is Wanda Maximoff from?",
        options:["Sokovia","Canada","Wakanda","USA"],
        ans:"Sokovia"
    }
];

export default ques;